Michael Fleming

in in

I'm an aspiring web developer and designer. I've been studying web since high school (5+ years) and I have gotten the opportunity to advance my knowledge while attending Fullsail University. I enjoy working with others as well as by myself and I'm very adaptable to either work environment. I love seeing what I can do with the web and I look forward to future projects whether it be with a company or freelance work.

- Web Design
- HTML 5
- jQuery
- Illustrator
- Coda
- Flash Builder
- MongoDB
- Front-end Design
- Premiere
- SASS
- CSS

- Web Development
- CSS3
- Angular.js
- PHP
- Dreamweaver
- ActionScript
- Databases
- Front-end Coding
- Google Docs
- OmniGraffle

- · Web Applications
- JavaScript
- Photoshop
- CodeIgniter
- Flash
- SQL
- Backend Development
- MAMP
- Google Chrome
- Sequel Pro

Experience

N/A

Freelance

11 / 2012 - Present

Pursued freelance projects for clients and/or myself that allowed me to further my knowledge of certain web technologies while also learning how to conduct myself in a business-like manner

Full Sail University

02 / 2012 - Present

Student

Education

Full Sail University

2011 - 2014

Bachelor of Science (BS), Web Design and Development

Seminole State College of Florida

2011 - 2011

N/A , Pre-Requisite courses